<resources>
    <string name="app_name">30 Day of cooking</string>
    <string name="recipe_name1">Ham and Gruyère Scones</string>
    <string name="recipe1">
Step 1\nCombine flour, sugar, baking powder, and salt in a large mixing bowl. Use a pastry cutter to cut butter into flour mixture until it resembles rice or coarse meal. Stir in ham and Gruyère until evenly mixed.
\nStep 2\nMoisten flour mixture with cream, until dough begins to come together. Add a bit more cream, milk, or water if dough seems dry.
\nStep 3\nTurn out on a floured work surface and fold dough onto itself. Gently stretch dough, turning and folding 3 or 4 times. Lightly flour a rolling pin and roll dough out 1/2- to 3/4-inch thick, turning dough a quarter turn occasionally.
\nStep 4\nCut scones with a lightly floured 3-inch biscuit cutter; press cutter straight down, without twisting. Pat dough scraps together and cut as needed. Line a baking sheet with parchment; place cut scones on the sheet.
\nStep 5\nWhisk egg, water, and pinch salt together in a small bowl. Brush tops of scones with egg wash, and refrigerate for about 20 minutes.
\nStep 6\nPreheat the oven to 235 degrees C. Brush the top of the scones with the egg mixture again.
\nStep 7\nBake scones in the center of the preheated oven until tops are crispy and lightly browned, 15 to 20 minutes. Serve warm or at room temperature. </string>
    <string name="recipe_name2">Chicken Salad</string>
    <string name="recipe2">
    ½ cup blanched slivered almonds\n
    ½ cup mayonnaise\n
    1 tablespoon lemon juice\n
    ¼ teaspoon ground black pepper\n
    2 cups chopped, cooked chicken meat\n
    1 stalk celery, chopped\n
        Step 1.\n
        Gather all ingredients.\n
        Step 2.\n
        Place almonds in a frying pan. Toast over medium-high heat, shaking frequently. Watch carefully, as they burn easily.\n
        Step 3.\n
        Mix together mayonnaise, lemon juice, and pepper in a medium bowl\n
        Step 4.\n
        Toss with chicken, toasted almonds, and celery\n
    </string>
    <string name="recipe_name3">Pasta Salad</string>
    <string name="recipe3">
    1 pound tri-colored spiral pasta\n
    1 (16 ounce) bottle Italian-style salad dressing\n
    6 tablespoons salad seasoning mix\n
    2 cups cherry tomatoes, diced\n
    1 green bell pepper, chopped\n
    1 red bell pepper, diced\n
    ½ yellow bell pepper, chopped\n
    1 (2.25 ounce) can black olives, chopped\n
        Step 1.\nGather all ingredients.\n
        Step 2.\nBring a large pot of lightly salted water to a boil. Cook pasta in the boiling water, stirring occasionally, until tender yet firm to the bite, about 10 to 12 minutes; rinse under cold water and drain.\n
        Step 3.\nWhisk Italian dressing and salad spice mix together until smooth. Combine pasta, tomatoes, bell peppers, and olives in a salad bowl.\n
        Step 4.\nPour dressing over salad and toss to coat.\n
        Step 5.\nFor the best flavor, refrigerate the pasta salad for 8 hours to overnight.\n
    </string>
    <string name="recipe_name4">Egg Fried Rice</string>
    <string name="recipe4">
    1 cup water\n
    2 tablespoons soy sauce\n
    ½ teaspoon salt\n
    1 cup uncooked instant rice\n
    1 teaspoon vegetable oil\n
    ½ onion, finely chopped\n
    ½ cup sliced green beans or peas\n
    1 large egg, lightly beaten\n
    ¼ teaspoon ground black pepper\n
        Step 1.\nBring water, soy sauce, and salt to a boil in a medium saucepan. Stir in instant rice and remove from heat. Cover and let stand for 5 minutes.\n
        Step 2.\nHeat oil in a medium skillet or wok over medium heat. Sauté onions and green beans in hot oil for 2 to 3 minutes. Pour in beaten egg and fry for 2 minutes, scrambling egg while it cooks. \n
        Step 3.\nAdd cooked rice to egg mixture; mix well. Season with pepper.\n
    </string>
</resources>